tutorcomp.com 2019-10-20

# Privacy Policy | Tutorcomp

This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms of Usage and shall apply to all the information collected on www.tutorcomp.com. All users of this website are expected to go through this policy and TutorComp presumes that you have read and accepted this policy when you use our services.

####  **1\. Personal Information – What do we collect?**

TutorComp would be required to know who you are to render our services that best suits you and your needs. To enable the services, either through browsing, or through any interaction including but not limited to emails, telephone calls or other correspondence, we seek your information that could personally identify you or could be used to personally identify you. You hereby accept and consent to the collection of such information by TutorComp. Without prejudice to the generality of the above, information collected by us from you may include but not limited to personal information about the student/parent/guardian including the first and last name, date of birth, age, sex, residential address, contact address, school information, parent/guardian first name and last name, telephone/cell number, email ID, credit card information, etc. TutorComp shall provide the student with a user name and a password, which should be kept confidential and should not be shared with any one. Safekeeping of your username and password is your responsibility and TutorComp shall not be responsible for any consequences of lost/stolen username and/ or password.

####  **2\. Why do we collect and how we use your information?**

TutorComp collects your personal information to help us serve you better. We use your personal information collected to provide personalised tutorial sessions for you, to improve your sessions, obtain feed backs from you, online fee payment, respond to your requests for schedule change to contact you in case of unavailability of tutor/ change of schedule etc. We may also use your information for improving our website and services and also for our marketing and promotional purposes. You may opt for not sharing certain information with us however you may not be able to utilise our services completely upon withholding information.

####  **3\. Storage and sharing of information**

All the information provided to TutorComp by you, including personal information or any sensitive personal data or any other information, is voluntary. TutorComp values your privacy and the information gathered shall be kept confidential by us. TutorComp does not share your personal contact information with unaffiliated third parties, However, we shall use the information collected for registration, managing your account, commercial purposes, research, statistical analysis and business intelligence purposes. Take note that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, your information could be collected and used by others. Although TutorComp attempt to protect your personal information, we do not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and that you do so at your own risk. However, once we receive your contents and information, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. TutorComp may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to protect our rights or property. Under certain circumstances, the Government or court may require the disclosure of information, including your personal information and TutorComp will be forced to comply especially in the interest of national security, criminal activities, law suits etc. We may also voluntarily disclose your personal information to the governmental authorities, if we believe that such disclosure is appropriate in the interest of national security, etc.

TutorComp may utilize reasonable physical, technical and administrative measures to safeguard the information that we collect. We shall retain the data as required or permitted by Government of India law and for its legitimate business purpose.

####  **4\. Tutor Sessions**

TutorComp does not encourage exchange of personal information during sessions. We do provide restricted information to your Tutors to enable them to provide you a better service. You are NOT required to provide your personally identifiable information like address, phone number, blood group, financial status, race, religion, email, social network IDs etc to the Tutor. We recommend parental guidance during sessions for students below 13 years of age. TutorComp does not in any way associate, contribute or be liable for any violation of privacy of the users in the event of any pornographic, disturbing contents or materials are uploaded by the users. TutorComp shall not be responsible for any voluntary information provided by you during the sessions.

####  **5\. Cookies**

TutorComp may use cookies in our website to identify our customers. Cookies are tiny files which are downloaded from our website and which reside in your computer. Cookies help us remember your preferences and helps us serve you better. We do not share or sell any information collected by the cookies. If you do not prefer to download cookies, kindly refer the help section of your browser on how to disable cookies. However, please note that some of our services may not function properly when cookies are disabled.

####  **6\. Modification**

TutorComp reserves all rights to modify this policy. You are requested to verify and update yourself in the event we modify our Privacy Policy statement. If you require to modify your data, the same can be done by sending the updated information to info@tutorcomp.com

####  **7\. Compliance**

This Privacy Policy is published in compliance with, (a) Section 43A of the Information Technology Act, 2000; (b) Regulation 4 of the Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Information) Rules, 2011 (the “SPI Rules”); (c) Regulation 3(1) of the Information Technology (Intermediaries Guidelines) Rules, 2011.

####  **8\. Consent to this policy**

You hereby agree and acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is a part of the Terms of Use of the Website and the other Services, and you unconditionally agree that becoming a User of the Website and its Services signifies your (i) assent to this Privacy Policy, and (ii) consent to TutorComp using, collecting, processing and/or Disclosing your Personal Information in the manner and for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

####  **9\. Changes to our policy**

If TutorComp decide to change this privacy policy, we will post on this page This policy was last modified on 5th Aug 2016.

####  **10\. Contacting Us**

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the below information info@TutorComp .com +1 646 546 5075 (US)
